lovepik.com 2019-06-24

# 

## Privacy Policy

### Welcome to Lovepik's Privacy Policy

On http://lovepik.com (from now on, will be referred as lovepik.com), visitor privacy is of our serious concern. This privacy policy page describes what kind of personal information may be received and collected by lovepik.com and how the information will be used. 

### How Lovepik Uses Personal Information

Generally, the User may browse the Website without providing any personal information. If the User registers on the Website, the data gathered will be incorporated to a file in Lovepik in order to manage the Website, provide its Services, offer certain functionalities associated to the status of User (the list of downloads, for instance), and send information to the User about the Services of Lovepik or its sponsors through newsletters (the subscription of which can be canceled by Users at any moment from their account). Lovepik doesn't gather information about the age or date of birth of their Users when they register. Consequently, there isn't a particular treatment aimed to underage Users. Lovepik is only aimed to full age Users. Any information received by Lovepik through Contact forms, Broken Link? forms, satisfaction surveys available on the Website, or through the email addresses lovepikvrf@gmail.com, will be incorporated to a Lovepik file and will only be used with the intention of answer- ing the questions, suggestions or complaints sent by the Users of the Website. Any information received by Lovepik through the Work With Us form available on the Website will be incorporated to a Lovepik file and will only be used with the purpose of managing the selection process of Lovepik personnel. The Website includes plugins that allow to perform some actions in social networks belonging to third parties such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or Google+ like sending a publication or show support to the Website, for instance. These plugins are displayed with the logo of their associated social network. If those plugins are accepted, the corresponding content will be sent to the adequate social network. The User may find information about how those plugins work and in what way the personal data is used in the privacy policies of these social networks. If the User doesn't wish these social networks to collect these personal data, the plugin shouldn't be accepted and the account should be abandoned before browsing the Website.

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at lovepikvrf@gmail.com. We will respond to your request within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Opt Out/Corrections

Upon your request, we will   
(a) correct or update your personal information;   
(b) stop sending emails to your email address;   
(c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account.  
You can make these requests at the customer information section, or emailing your request to lovepik.com’s Customer Support department at lovepikvrf@gmail.com. Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.

### Protection of Your Personal Information

The Personal Information that you provide in connection with the use of the Site is protected in several ways. Access by you to your account profile is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. You should strive to use a strong, alpha-numeric password which you should not divulge to anyone. Your Personal Information resides on a secure server that only selected Lovepik personnel and contractors have access to via password. Your Personal Information is encrypted whenever it is transmitted to Lovepik. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We strive to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. While we use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can send email to us at lovepikvrf@gmail.com.

### Privacy Complaints

Lovepik takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Lovepik has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Information.In your letter please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Lovepik Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact our Privacy Officer at lovepikvrf@gmail.com.
